<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>firestarme.dispensarymod</packageId>
  <name>Dispensary Mod</name>
  <author>Firestarme</author>
  <url>https://github.com/Firestarme/DispensaryMod</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.5</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>1.5.1.0 [29-06-2024]

Want to lift the mood of your colonists with a few smokeleaf joints? 
Want to make your pawns wedding just that little bit wilder with a stock of yayo?
Or just make your millions by tempting your neighbours with the scourage of flake.

Do all this while carefully avoiding addiction by keeping your drugs under lock and key!

Adds the objects:

**Dispensary**
Links to a stockpile to provide drugs to pawns that are authorised to use them via the vanilla drug policy system.
This building fits on to a wall and blocks access to this protected stockpile.

**Drug Room Door**
A special door that blocks access to pawns assigned to specific drug policies.
This can be used to keep at-risk pawns out of the protected drug stockpile.
Beware though! anyone can pass the door if it is unpowered (will act like a standard door).
Unlocked with the reasearch 'Autodoors'

[Changelog]

######################

1.5.1.1 [17-07-2024]
----------------------
Added additional null check to JobGiver_GetDrugsFromDispensary.TryGiveJob


1.5.1.0 [29-06-2024]
----------------------
Updated to rimworld 1.5
Drugroom door now blocks non-colonists
Drugroom door now only clears a pawns reachability cache when its settings/state is changed
  This should preserve pawn caches much more often, improving performance
  This also helps to avoid pawns thinking they are still blocked when the settings have been changed

1.4.1.4 [17-1-24]  -1.4 Latest Supported version
----------------------
Added additional null checks when assigning a 'get drug from dispensary' job

1.4.1.2 [31-10-23]  
----------------------
Fixed error when pawns search for dispensary when none exist.
Fixed pawns not checking requested drug is available at closest dispensary.

1.4.1.1 [28-10-23]  
----------------------
Fixed dispensory not blocking temperature when installed over wall.
Fixed some unexpected behaviour when drawing dispensory placeworker ghosts.

1.4.1.0 [04-10-23]  
----------------------
Inital Release (for rimworld 1.4)

######################
  </description>
</ModMetaData>